{
    "subject": "resource/Victor_Hugo",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Hernani_(drama)",
    "human_readable": "Victor Hugo's notable work is 'Hernani (drama)'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8769059777259827,
            "question": "Name a famous work by Victor Hugo."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8535739183425903,
            "question": "What is the title of Victor Hugo's notable work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.673957109451294,
            "question": "Besides 'Hernani', what other works did Victor Hugo write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5001199245452881,
            "question": "What themes are often explored in Victor Hugo's works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44883713126182556,
            "question": "Is 'Hernani' considered a novel or a play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43430718779563904,
            "question": "Who wrote 'Hernani'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4087757170200348,
            "question": "What genre does 'Hernani' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3439999222755432,
            "question": "What is Victor Hugo known for writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30483144521713257,
            "question": "What impact did 'Hernani' have on literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2769899368286133,
            "question": "In what literary period was Victor Hugo active?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Victor Hugo's notable work is 'Hernani (drama)'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8038_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did 'Hernani' have on literature?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8038_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Victor Hugo known for writing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8038_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does 'Hernani' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8038_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8038_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8038_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8038_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8038_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8038_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8038_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8038_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8038_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8038_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8038_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Victor Hugo, including his works and literary achievements. The text states that he was at the forefront of the Romantic literary movement with his play Cromwell and drama Hernani, indicating that \"Hernani\" is indeed a notable work by Hugo."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Victor Hugo's notable work is 'Hernani (drama)'. \" Both `94.txt` and `81.txt` mention his play \"Hernani\" as a significant piece of his literary output."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}